Downloaded @ subs4free.club
What makes
a person extraordinary?
Everyone wants to be normal.
But no one wants to be ordinary.
And what is normal?
We all see the pretty
pictures on our feeds.
Normal party, normal family,
normal adorable little girl.
But, there’s always
more behind the facade.
Most of the time
Lindy seems quite normal.
But buried deep in
her DNA she has a gift.
Some call it a condition,
or even worse, a disorder,
that’s just
waiting to be activated
and it makes
her anything but normal.
When people do bad things,
Lindy cannot control herself.
Maybe if she’d had
that normal loving family,
she could have
been extraordinary.
But, just like Lindy, mommy
and daddy had their own demons.
Whether it was that mummy’s
pills made her so sleepy,
or that daddy got so
angry when he drank too much,
we’ll never know.
But whatever it was, Lindy
never got the love she needed.
Instead, she got
angrier and angrier,
and her disorder
got worse and worse.
And then her parents
got her diagnosis.
The doctors called it
Intermittent Explosive Disorder.
She could not
live safely in the world,
and no one would
be safe around her.
So to live at all,
she would have to live alone,
isolated from others
till the cure could be found.
The huge amount of cortisol
coursing through Lindy’s body,
made her faster than
normal, stronger than normal,
which made her
incredibly attractive
to certain interested parties.
But her condition also
made her extremely volatile
and far, far
angrier than normal.
Lindy had a hair trigger.
Once provoked, she would snap.
Until she could gain control,
she was no use to anyone.
Her life as
a human lab rat began.
The results were mixed.
So they thought,
maybe the military
would give her the structure
to channel her unique gifts.
Or maybe not.
All right, stop!
Get off!
Get off him, now!
Stop means, stop!
They were
so kind and supportive.
It’s a wonder it didn’t help.
Of course, all these
cures only made it worse.
You would think they’d
learn not to piss her off.
It was looking more and more
like they would just lock her up
and throw away the key.
Lindy would be alone, forever.
And then a breakthrough,
a chance to be normal.
The treatment was
brutal, barbaric, outrageous
and surprisingly effective.
Like you don’t care
I see you right there
Tryna watch my joyride
This is ridiculous.
I’ve been waiting
here for five fucking minutes.
How hard is it
to find my fucking car keys?
I know, I know. I’m sorry,
but give me just a minute, okay?
Is "fucking idiot" part
of your job description?
I know,
I’m-- I’m sorry, sir...
There’s
like a million keys here.
And apparently you’re too dumb
even for a minimum wage job.
Is this your key?
Yes, that’s
my key, you fucking moron.
Hey, this is my car!
Yeah, I think
you forgot something.
-What?
-Your manners.
-Sorry, is this your key?
- Huh?
Yes, that’s my
key, you fucking moron.
Don’t expect a tip!
That she your princess
Um, Justin?
Hi. I’m Lindy.
Hey!
Yeah, actually I’m
not staying so... um,
I thought a date might be fun,
but I’m not in
the right head-space,
so I didn’t want to bail,
without saying something,
’cause I’m not a total bitch.
Okay.
-So...
You know it’s funny? Uh...
This isn’t even
the worst date I’ve ever had.
Yeah. I feel bad--
I’m sorry about that--
Herpes!
Yeah, herpes,
chlamydia and, um, warts.
Uh...
Okay.
This girl just kept listing off,
all the sexually transmitted
infections she had. It was...
it was unexpected.
Yeah, I mean, warts
generally are, aren’t they?
You don’t have
a disaster date story?
Uh, me? No,
I don’t date that much. No.
Oh, is that ’cause you’re always
leaving before they start?
No, you’re doing quite well.
I normally don’t even come in.
Oh, why not?
I hate people.
Like who?
I don’t know. People who--
who talk with their mouth full
and-- and, uh, people who, who
chew too loudly, people who hum.
Um, men who wear
jeans with flip-flops--
I can’t stand
people who walk too slow.
Yeah. Exactly.
Or tell you to have a nice day.
Yeah! Like, fuck off
I might not want a nice day.
Or, uh, people
that talk in elevators.
Yeah, that’s bad.
Yeah, aside from people
that fart in elevators.
That’s-- That’s worse.
Do you fart in elevators?
Do you fart?
No, I’m from
England, we don’t...
Are we ready to order?
I’m actually not
staying, so I don’t know.
Sir, I’m afraid if
she won’t be dining with you,
we will need the table back.
Okay.
Now.
Uh...
Okay, um...
Okay, I’ll just, um...
I’ll just have the chicken
really quickly then.
Uh...
Fish please,
without the pine nuts.
We don’t do substitutions.
Oh, no. I’m-- I’m--
I’m allergic, so...
It’s restaurant policy.
Uh, okay. The pasta, please.
There is a walnut sauce.
Uh,
how about the pork chop?
Pistachio crust.
Fuck me. Perhaps you can suggest
something that might work.
Please don’t
take that tone with me.
-No, I’m not.
-Sir. You are.
You’re making it impossible
for me to impress my date
and it’s embarrassing.
How about the chicken?
Sure.
Thank you.
Let me know if
you need anything else.
Thank you.
You know, if you were planning
to stab her with that knife,
it’d be totally cool with me.
Look, I have to pee actually.
-Okay.
- I’ll be right back.
I know, right?
A guy just told
his wife he is having an affair.
Some old woman’s
dentures got stuck in her steak.
But hold up, you should see
the first date I just served.
I gave the guy some attitude
and he practically
cried into his napkin.
Yeah. And his date just sat
there and watched him squirm.
Oh, my God.
It was so embarrassing.
I mean, screwing with the
customers isn’t fun anymore.
It’s like my own
private freak show.
The guy had, like,
allergies to pretty much
everything on the menu.
It was pathetic.
I know.
Total losers.
Anyway...
She’ll call you back.
Fuck!
-
Oh! Ain’t you
a fine little piece...
Ow!
Fuck!
It’s not working.
Okay. Fix it!
You’re probably just
building up a tolerance.
No, I’m not.
Look, this is cutting-edge,
avant-garde treatment.
Okay. Well,
I’m sure you’ll get
the Nobel Prize once
you’re dead.
Is that a threat?
Can you fix it or not?
-All right.
- Okay.
Here.
Your emotions must
be running pretty high,
in order for you
to override the system.
Yeah. I have an unnaturally
high level of cortisol,
so my emotions are
running high all the time.
But you cannot keep
using biochemistry as an excuse,
all the time.
So, I’m assuming that the date
was a disappointment then?
Given that its primary function,
was to test if I could partake
in a customary social situation
without beating
the shit out of someone,
then yeah, I would say yeah.
It was a-- it was
a real disappointment.
How badly did you hurt him?
I didn’t
even get round to him.
Who did you get around to?
A waitress. Look, it doesn’t
matter. Your thing failed.
Lindy, this is not
a cure. I’ve told you that.
The only way we’re
going to make progress,
is if you begin to
reconcile with your past.
I’ve told you my story.
But there’s a difference,
between talking about your past,
and actually working through it.
Asphyxiation?
Jugular bleed.
Classy.
Here you go.
I’ve upped the voltage,
but there’s only so much
that the human body can take.
You don’t care about
me. I’m just an experiment.
Why would I risk my
life’s work if I didn’t care?
And why won’t you admit
that you really like this guy?
Because I didn’t.
Okay.
Anyway, it doesn’t matter.
I think last night proved that
your exposure therapy
didn’t work.
What-- what-- what
would you like me to do? Hmm?
Would you like me to
put leeches on your skin?
Would you like me to drill
a hole,
in your head to release
the demons?
Would you like me to
make you drink your own urine?
Actually tried that.
That’s disgusting.
Anyway, I think
that really you need to admit,
that the answer to all of
your problems
is close,
human connection.
Penis is not
gonna fix me, Dr. Freud.
Um, I just--
And I’ve tried that as well.
You like this guy, so
for once have a relationship.
Oh, please fuck off.
I’m talking about love.
No, I don’t want a boyfriend!
We both know I’d end up knocking
his teeth down his throat.
Maybe you won’t, but I don’t
know why you would walk away,
from somebody
who made you feel something.
Ugh!
Okay, I’m walking away
from you,
’cause you’re getting on
my nerves.
Thank you.
See you next week.
Yeah, I can’t wait.
Looks so good.
Thank you so much.
Not bad, huh?
-Well...
Not a shitty waitress in sight!
No.
I’m glad you called.
I’d hate to miss a second chance
to disappoint a pretty face.
How are you planning
on doing that?
I don’t know.
Depends if you find lame-ass
accountants cool or not.
Well, that depends.
Who do you work for?
I work for a private
company. This guy named Barry.
You? What do you do?
I used to work in Security.
Okay. So you know your way
around a pair of handcuffs?
Less BDSM, more...
bouncer in a crappy bar.
You’re not
a bouncer!
Yeah! What?
What do you weigh?
Like a Buck-O-Eight?
-It’s not about size Justin.
-No?
Don’t know what you’ve heard...
Then what’s it about?
Other things,
like speed and endurance,
fearlessness, things like that.
Okay. What happened?
Mmm...
You crazy bitch!
Um...
I’m currently
seeking a new career path.
Oh, you got fired.
Yes. Well, it wasn’t my fault.
It-- I mean, it was
actually entirely my fault.
I don’t know.
My heart wasn’t in it.
No?
What is your heart in?
I like photography.
Yeah? What do
you take pictures of?
Mostly, naked accountants.
I don’t know, just
people going about their lives.
I-- I just-- I take pictures
on my phone sometimes for fun.
It’s not really...
It sounds kinda
voyeuristic to me.
Oh, I am wanking, constantly.
Well, uh... I’m sorry if
I can seem kind of boring.
Thank you for
apologizing. I am quite bored.
There’s nothing
I can do about it.
There are a couple of
things that you could do.
What can I do?
Maybe this is a mistake.
I have to warn you,
I’m really crap at dating.
How bad could you be?
Very bad.
I’m not scared of you.
Well, maybe you should be.
Oh, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait! Hold...
It’s, um...
They’re-- they’re...
They’re a...
Is that like a...
Like a kinky thing or?
No. No.
Okay.
Uh, look,
the thing is Justin, I...
-Hey.
-Um...
Hey...
It’s not...
a big...
deal.
-It’s okay.
-Yeah?
Good morning.
More like afternoon.
You look so cute
when you’re asleep,
and I didn’t wanna wake you up.
Not really used
to being called cute.
No? Well, you are.
When you let your guard down.
Your place is weird.
Ah, it’s--
you know, it’s good weird.
What’s with all
the plastic plates and cups?
You just move in?
No, uh, just,
I-- I hate washing up.
Well, in addition to the world’s
most expensive Danish,
I got you a little something.
Wow. Am I amazing in bed?
Yeah.
Oh, my God!
Oh, no. That’s too much.
No, it’s not.
Wow!
-You like it?
-Love it!
Thank you.
Oh, um,
by the way, last night...
I-- I never do that.
No?
No. I mean, never.
Well, I’m-- I’m glad you did.
You are...
you’re full of surprises.
The least of which is,
um, this whole situation.
You, uh, you wanna elaborate?
Now that we know
each other better.
Yeah. Um...
You know what?
You don’t have to. I’m sorry.
No! I will. Uh, it’s a new
treatment for this... thing.
You’re not gonna
die on me, are you?
No. No, no, no.
That’d be just
my luck, you know?
I meet the most
amazing woman in the city
and you got six months to live?
No, I’ve got, um...
an impulse control problem.
And that helps
me to not have it.
Like Tourette’s?
No. Um, just
tiny bit more intense.
Okay.
Uh, well, I mean,
have you tried meditation
or something?
Yeah, sort of.
Yoga...
Medication...
Extreme sports...
You know, I’ve tried
like, a whole lot of things,
picked up lots of useless skills
and, um, that’s
the thing that-- that helps.
Well, I don’t see
anything wrong with you.
Mm-mmm. No, no,
no. I gotta go to work.
Well, can’t
you say you’re sick?
No, I can’t. Barry
will totally bust my balls.
Oh, okay. Well, no, leave--
leave the balls exactly
as they are, they were good.
Um, but can’t you say
that something came
up with another client?
Well, I only have one...
and he pays for
my exclusivity, so...
-Okay?
-Okay.
Come to my place tonight.
Yeah? I’ll cook.
I’m a fucking ninja
with a piece of halibut.
Yes, yes, yes!
I could feel this way
Touch as much you want
-Oh, my God!
-No! It’s fine!
-It’s fine!
-What?
It’s fine. It’s fine! Relax.
You’re early!
Yes, I was excited to see you!
Why?
Because you’re a genius.
You’re a bald
and burnished genius.
I’m cured.
Oh, you saw him again?
And, I had an impulse, but...
it wasn’t a
breaking his legs,
smash his face in, slamming--
Actually, there
was a bit of slamming.
But it was warm
and romantic and...
and filthy.
This is progress.
Very good.
Very good?
It’s brilliant!
Listen, I took the vest off.
Wow! Wow.
A couple more weeks,
-I’m not even gonna need this.
-That’s great!
But I think it’s
temporary euphoria.
I can’t stop thinking about him.
His hands, his face,
his hair smells really amazing--
Oh, my God! The penis!
I almost called
you in the middle of it.
It, like,
unfurled itself, like--
to ten times its length,
like-- like a travel umbrella!
-I’ve only ever heard of that.
-Yeah!
-Never actually seen it!
-No.
-Grower. Amazing!
-I wouldn’t know...
Yeah. Wow.
I didn’t know those existed.
Oh, and he’s
cooking me dinner tonight.
-Stop it.
-Hmm. Fish.
Fish! But you don’t like fish.
No, but people change.
They do.
-I’ve changed.
It’s true.
Okay, why don’t we sit down
and let’s have
a little chat about this?
-Because-- Okay, all right.
-Boring and snooze.
Because I want to celebrate!
Can we open
a bottle of something?
No, it’s ten
o’clock in the morning.
Okay, you’re being a bad friend.
I’m not your friend.
I’m your psychiatrist.
I finally want
to talk about dick,
you should be salivating.
Gross. No, look,
sit down, please, all right?
No, I don’t
need a session today.
Yes, you do,
because you’re manic
and it’s making
me incredibly anxious.
-And I’m worried about you.
-Don’t be anxious.
-I am though.
-I love you.
Okay. Uh, love you too.
-I love you more!
- Oh, boy.
Hello?
-Justin?
No. This is Detective Vicars.
Homicide.
-
But how do
you know it was murder?
His body was
found in a dumpster,
with two gunshot
wounds to the head.
Were you together very long?
Tonight was
gonna be our third date.
He was-- was
gonna cook me dinner.
Fish.
Salmon?
Halibut.
Hmm.
You know any of his friends,
family or coworkers?
No. I-- I know
he’s an accountant.
He... was an accountant.
But he only had one client.
Some guy named Barry.
We’re gonna find who did this.
Let’s not give
the lady false hope.
Statistically, it’s unlikely.
I’m not giving her anything.
I’m reassuring
her we’re gonna do our best.
Some people prefer honesty.
Some people prefer compassion.
Can I see him?
No. Family only right now.
Can I talk to his family?
We haven’t been
able to find anyone yet.
But then who’s
gonna mind if I see him?
Policy’s gonna mind.
-Those are the rules.
- She loves rules.
Look, we really are
very sorry, for your loss.
-Aah!
-
Sounds like
your guy was involved
in some pretty sketchy business.
Dodged a bullet or two.
All right, listen.
Just give us a call,
if you remember anything else.
Thanks.
What the fuck-hell was that?
She was upset.
She’s grieving, I’m-- I’m
just trying to comfort her.
I think she’s angry.
I don’t think so.
That’s why you like her.
You like ’em with
a little rage bottled up inside.
Better in bed,
until it blows up in
your stupid-ass face.
"I’m a big strong policeman."
"Let me embrace you, and
comfort your grieving vagina."
I don’t
wanna comfort a vagina.
It’s not a big deal.
Stop!
You fixed me, now he’s dead!
Ah! It’s not working.
I’m going to get you a sedative.
Now, you have
to stop shocking yourself.
Lindy? Lindy?
I’m not scared of you.
Lindy?
Where is it?
You’re holding it.
How do you feel?
I want to crush
your skull with my bare hands.
I’m sorry about Justin.
I mean, they acted
like it was no big deal.
Who?
The police.
Well, don’t focus on
them. Focus on yourself.
It’s obvious
they thought his boss
had something to do with it.
Which, I mean, of course.
Right? He only had one client.
That’s a bit weird, isn’t it?
I am sure they’ll figure it out.
Fuck them!
No, I need to
find out who did this.
I have to talk to Justin’s boss.
What if
you just took a moment,
-and you felt--
-What if
I just snapped your neck?
I’m gonna find
the fuckers who did this.
If you go down that path,
you are never,
ever going to get better.
Fuck.
You’re gonna kill somebody.
-You’re fucking right I am.
-Wait!
I have to
tell you something--
Look! Some people cry. Some
people drink.
Some people write
shit poetry. I hurt people.
Might as well
put it to good use.
Vicars.
Hi,
Detective Vicars?
I need to talk to you.
I-- I think I have more
information but I’m scared.
Can you come
meet me at my place?
Yeah. Yeah,
we’ll be right there.
Hello?
Hi, Lindy,
it’s Detective Vicars.
Lindy?
Hello Detective. You’re
angry, right?
Why are you stealing evidence?
Because I want to
find out what happened.
That’s my job.
Uh-huh. How’s
that going for you?
I found you, didn’t I?
-What?
- My partner wants to bring you
in for interfering with an
investigation, and robbery and
probably a whole
bunch of other stuff
’cause she’s
ridiculously thorough.
But I wanted to give you the
chance to come in on your own
and clear up this
misunderstanding.
Without all the, you know, jail.
She’s on her way up now.
-Fucking balls. Where are you?
-I’m parked out front.
She’s not going
to shoot me, is she?
No, of course not.
Freeze!
-Fuck!
Then again, she might...
So here’s what’s gonna happen.
You’re gonna put your arms over
your head, I’m gonna cuff you,
I’m gonna take
you down to the station,
-and then I’m gonna book you.
-What if I have other plans?
I’ll fucking shoot you.
And then waste a bunch
of time writing up a report,
instead of hunting
down your boyfriend’s killer.
Wasn’t actually
my boyfriend yet.
Commitment issues?
It was early days.
As if dating in
the city wasn’t hard enough.
You finally find a good man,
and boom,
two bullets to the brain.
Your partner is a trip, Vicars.
Hey, Nevin...
Is that?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Give me the phone.
Please don’t tell me,
you just called
this murder suspect--
Sorry. Having a bad day.
Freeze!
-I didn’t kill him!
-
Hello?
- Oh. Hi, Detective.
Lindy, is everything
okay up there? Is Nevin okay?
Little
busy at the moment.
Busy doing what?
Remembering
how to drive stick.
What?
-Stupid motherfucker.
-Ow, ow, ow.
Holy shit! I know that sound.
That’s a McLaren 600LT Spider?
It’s a car.
A really fast one.
Are you still on the phone
with that kooky cuntcicle?
Fucking go! Go! Go!
Where did you learn to drive?
You even trying to catch her?
I’m flooring it!
Guys, it’s
quite hard to concentrate
with you two bickering.
Oh!
-Oh, crap!
-
-Come on, Lindy.
- Ooh.
I think I’m starting to get
the hang of this stick shift.
Oh, shit. Reverse!
Damn it!
Lindy, please stay on the phone.
I’m trying to help you.
Okay. I really
have to concentrate now,
so, it’s been
really nice catching up.
No, wait! You go
through with this and you’re--
You’re on your own.
Same as always.
Lindy!
Damn it!
Shit!
I’m trying to help you. You’re
going to get somebody killed.
If you think I had anything to
do with Justin’s death,
then you’re shitter at your
jobs than I thought.
We don’t think you killed
Justin...
Speak for yourself!
Whoa! Argh!
Get ’em!
- Yeah!
Ah! The fuck...
-I’m not doing it.
-Don’t bitch out!
Fine! Fine! Fine!
-Fuck.
-
If you
can’t ascertain the cause,
of the outbreak,
then you have no idea,
how many zombies
you’ll have to kill over time.
A lightsaber
would solve both problems.
We specified
a real-world scenario.
Yeah, a real zombie apocalypse.
Besides, there’s no way
to recharge the lightsaber’s
Diatium power cell
after it ran out.
Diatium power cells
don’t run out of energy.
They recycle it.
Who’s in charge around here?
I’m-- I-- I’m the manager.
If you’re the manager
then you’re the last person,
I want to talk to.
I need someone who actually
knows what they’re doing.
Who’s the biggest
geek you’ve got in this place?
-Andy.
Andy.
Okay, so what? Forget
your password or something?
No.
It’s more, the man
I loved was murdered
and I stole
his phone from the police,
and now I’ve got to
track down the bad guy
before they do, so
I can kill the shit out of them.
Oh! Cool.
And... we’re in.
Oh, wow. You’re good.
Obviously.
Not much here, no
history. This must be a burner.
Your boyfriend
a drug dealer or something?
No, accountant.
I mean, he wasn’t--
We weren’t... yet. You know.
Yeah. Right, right. I get it.
-I don’t.
-Did your mouth just fart, Doug?
Sorry.
The last seven calls,
came from
an abandoned building downtown.
-Shady.
-What does that mean?
I’m not sure.
Lets see who owns it.
Barry Kasparzki. Whoa!
FBI files showed
ties to arms dealers.
Holy shit!
That’s the guy.
How much do I owe you?
Trust me, you can’t afford me.
Thanks.
Oh.
Boys, boys, boys!
Whatever it is
you’re fighting over,
I’m sure we can all talk it out.
Money...
Yeah. You know, like bets?
Oh! Duh.
Is it too late to put
a dollar on the other one?
Just ’cause
you’re a bit of a bleeder
and you drop
your left when you hook.
What’s going on?
Oh, are you Barry? I guess so.
Just, you seem like,
you have
the biggest dick in here, so...
What do you want?
Well, I wanted
to pick your brains,
about the phone
calls you have with the...
accountant that works for you.
Did you kill him?
What are you? Cop? Fed?
Oh no, girlfriend.
I mean, I say girlfriend.
We went on,
like, two dates but...
you know, I was really
hopeful, I was crossing fingers.
I didn’t kill any accountant.
-But you know who did.
-Probably!
Well, amazing!
I mean, that saves me
a massive headache. Barry!
You’re a sweetheart.
I didn’t say I’d tell you.
Oh, seriously? Are you gonna
make me go through the whole,
face-stomping,
bone-breaking routine?
Okay, fine.
I tell you what.
How about I beat
three of your best guys,
and you tell me the name?
Sounds like fun.
You, you and you.
But not three in a row.
All at the same time.
I like a man who challenges me.
Okay, so what
are the, like, rules?
No rules.
Oh.
All right.
Oh!
Aah!
-
Lucky guess.
That’s enough!
Fight’s over!
Everybody out!
If he had a bigger Adam’s apple,
this’d be really working for me.
You don’t mind, do you?
I’m just a bit
parched after that.
Oh! I needed that.
Okay, you were gonna
tell me who killed Justin?
Those men back there,
they work for me,
they respect me and
they pay tribute to me.
They do this,
because they know,
that I am a man of my word.
Now...
Business like this,
I like to keep private.
’Cause the truth is,
all that I have is
because of one thing,
and one thing only.
And that is...
that I have never
been a man of my word.
So, if you’ll excuse me,
I don’t like to
get business on my suit.
Okay.
What is it about gross old men
always underestimating women?
Interesting ball color.
What we calling that? Ox-blood?
Claret?
Just like a woman,
straight for the nuts!
No. I only do
that when I’m in hurry.
Although, evolution hasn’t
really been kind to you guys,
putting the on-off switch,
dangling around in front
for any predator
to come by and flick.
Now, who killed him?
I don’t know.
Don’t be silly!
Gareth Fizel!
Yeah, he’s my boss.
Why would
he kill his accountant?
Maybe he was skimming the books.
Look, even the government,
ain’t dumb
enough to go after Fizel.
Are you really that stupid?
You know what? I think
I am exactly that stupid.
-
You enjoying that?
Mmm. Background check came in.
Your li’l girlfriend,
she’s got a history of violence.
Assault. Harassment.
Interesting job history
too. Classified-type shit.
So she’s got skills
and an anger issue.
Not a great combo.
I still don’t think,
she’s the type to blow
her boyfriend’s head off.
Hope not, or else you’re next.
She’s got a short fuse.
Doesn’t make her a murderer.
That’s what happens
when you don’t follow protocol.
Sometimes common
sense trumps protocol.
Nah. I’m good being the superior
one in this relationship.
Wha-- Hey! What
am I supposed to eat?
I’ll see what I can swipe from
the gunshot victim next door.
Always taking such good
care of me. Thank you, partner.
Aw, allergic to latex?
You’re no fun.
Wow! Impressive
urine output. Good for you.
Oh, don’t bother.
I’ll run away and
you’ll get yourself all
emasculated trying to catch me.
Here. I did get a bouquet,
but I gave it to
this woman in the elevator.
Just been diagnosed
with something horrible
and couldn’t stop
crying. It was really awkward.
Glad to see you’re all right.
I wanted to say thank
you for warning me and--
I wasn’t warning you.
I was giving you a chance
to do the right thing.
Well, thank you for
giving me the chance.
Look, I found
out who killed Justin.
Who?
Gareth Fizel.
You got any proof?
Well, obviously
not the sort of person
who gives a fuck about proof.
What do you know about him?
Billionaire recluse
with his fingers in a bunch
of different illegal pies.
He’s pretty much untouchable.
Oh, I’m gonna touch him.
Hard.
And a lot. And not in
a way he’s gonna enjoy.
Where can I find him?
Why you doing this?
Is this Justin really
worth you risking your life for?
Yeah, it was early
days. I didn’t know him.
I didn’t know half
the shit he was caught up in.
But I do know,
he was a decent guy.
He didn’t
deserve to die like that.
Nobody does.
Well, no, but...
Most people make me
want to run away screaming,
or snap their fingers
off. He was...
He was nice.
He was-- He was really nice.
There’s lots of
nice guys out there.
Yeah.
They’re all frightened of me.
He wanted to cook me fish.
The Imperion Tower. Downtown.
Thank you.
I can’t let you go there.
You’re not in a great
position to stop me, are you?
But I am.
Get back!
Get back here right now!
Stop!
Sorry.
Bitch, get back here!
Fuck.
Shh!
Ow!
Fuck!
Shh! Stop it. Stop it.
Freeze!
Don’t move, don’t
breathe, don’t fucking fart!
Oh, come on.
You’re not
gonna start shit in here.
I will shoot you.
Put the gun down.
Why would I do that?
Because I want you to be ready.
Ready for what?
This!
-Catch!
-
Freeze!
Don’t you dare!
Don’t do it.
-Seriously?
-I trust you!
Aah!
Oh.
Can I help you?
Gareth Fizel.
There’s no one
here by that name.
Okay.
It’s gonna be a lot
less painful for you,
if you just point me
in the right direction.
Good evening.
Can I be of assistance?
Mr. Delacroix, this woman...
is asking for a Mr. Fizel.
And she threatened me.
You’re fired.
For what?
Your tone. Miss?
Right this way.
That was some
pretty epic dick swinging.
That’s strange.
I would’ve thought,
the big cheese
would be on the top floor.
He is.
-Aah!
-
Ow!
Clean blow to my brachial
plexus nerve group. Good one.
Um...
You must be Security,
unless this is some
really fucked up date.
Head of. And you are?
About to pee my pants.
I had, like, four
Red Bulls on the way here.
Is that what
the drain in the floor is for?
What are these for?
That is a really
bad idea to take those.
-I need them.
-What for?
A bad heart.
Well, they’re mine now.
Why are you here?
I need to see your boss.
Regarding what?
He killed Justin.
Justin who?
His accountant.
Why would
he have killed your Justin?
Oh, I don’t know.
Boring everyday, bean counter
who’s cooking the books
for a shady arms dealer,
suddenly assassinated
and tossed in a dumpster.
Sounds like he had
information to disclose.
Seemed like a solid lead.
I mean, that and Barry told me.
Are you a relation
of the deceased?
No. I was...
-Not, we were...
-I see.
-Do you?
-No.
Nor do I desire to.
I am going to give you a chance
to vacate the premises,
-peacefully.
-
What if I don’t?
You will find out what
the drainage system is for.
And I will be keeping those.
-
My life vest...
I need my vest.
Apologies for the disturbance.
We’ve had a visitor, a woman.
She’s peculiar.
I need to get out of the car.
Can you let me out of the car?
Look, miss, I don’t
want to seem overly familiar,
but I gotta take you home.
Unlock this door and let me out!
Asking about an accountant.
A concern?
Let me out of
the car for your sake!
-Miss!
-Let me out!
Let me out!
I wasn’t sure
who may have been aware,
of her presence
here, so I opted to let her go.
But enough of
a concern to bother me with.
-
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry!
More like an unknown variable.
You know... I don’t
like unknown variables.
Deal with her.
Please help me?
Oh, fuck!
What are you doing here?
I lost my device.
Do you have another
here? I really need it. Please?
What happened to the lamp?
I figured, if things
got really bad, I could
bite down on both ends.
Don’t do that.
Sorry.
Thanks.
Have you seen
that movie Old Yeller?
Uh, yeah. It’s a classic.
I’ve never seen it,
but I know how it ends.
So if I... try anything,
kill me.
If I make this thing for you,
will you stop
going after this guy?
No.
But I can promise more
innocent people won’t get hurt
along the way.
Okay.
Do you want some Chinese food?
There’s Kung Pao chicken
and sweet and sour... something,
and some... egg
rolls and all that.
You should eat something.
Don’t touch
the shrimp fried rice.
-That’s mine.
-
I’ll get the vest.
Je-- Jesus!
What are you doing?
I’m hiding from
the beat cops down the street.
What are you doing?
Is sitting outside my apartment,
some kind of police foreplay?
Are you wearing my knickers?
I’m doing my job.
Oh.
I see we’ve taken down
another major drug kingpin.
He got sent home from school
for setting the class pet free.
Hmm. Hamster?
Rabbit. Hey, listen to me.
There’s some pretty nasty guys
in the hospital, you know, and
their description of
the deranged psycho
who put them there matches you.
What? Come on. Little old me?
How could you possibly think
I could do anything like that?
Don’t fuck
around with me, Lindy.
Okay, but not now,
I need you to look after this.
I’m not dumping
evidence for you!
I’m not asking you to.
Look, I’m-- I’m
giving you the chance
to turn yourself in here.
Okay, I will! Just not yet.
Hey, listen to me.
Fizel’s not some
dickbag gangster, okay?
He’s going to be looking for you
and he’s going to kill you.
Right. Well, he already tried.
I think someone has
been in my apartment--
Right, that’s it.
-It ain’t your choice anymore.
-No, no, no, no, no.
That’s a very
bad idea. I’ve got...
this condition. Okay?
It makes me snap. I can’t
control it and I hurt people.
I wear this thing,
that gives me electric shocks,
so that I can stop it happening.
But, really, I really
don’t want to hurt you
or anybody else.
I don’t think you’d hurt me.
-No?
-No.
Would you leave
me on my own with him?
-Yeah.
-Bollocks!
Well, I don’t think
you’d hurt him either.
You sure?
What that thing feel like?
Come on?
-What are you--
-Here.
-
Okay, you know
what that tells me?
I’m way more
screwed up than you thought.
No. No, it tells me
that you’d rather hurt yourself
than somebody else.
Nevin says
I treat you different
because you’re a woman.
She says...
I’m going easy on you.
Is she right?
I treat you different
because you are different.
Nobody is looking for me now.
Lindy!
Whoa!
What’s that?
Dad?
fuck!
Lindy, listen to me!
I’m a little
busy at the moment.
Look, Lindy I don’t
wanna play games anymore.
You have to stop
looking for Justin’s killer.
You’re gonna get hurt.
I know what you’re capable of.
I read all
about it in your file--
Okay. Are you done looking me up
on some bullshit database?
’Cause, listen, Detective.
I’m gonna do what I need to do.
Lindy I don’t wanna
see you wind up dead.
Just let us do our job.
So, what?
Does that mean you are gonna
go in and arrest Fizel?
Yes, thought not.
Fuck.
I was hoping to see you.
You like lobster?
Uh, I always thought
it was overrated and overpriced.
Most people don’t realize
that lobster’s belong in
the same biological phylum
as cockroaches.
They are both anthropods
with segmented bodies.
They both have the same compound
eyes and jointed legs.
Even their meat is the same.
Lobsters must be boiled alive.
Cockroaches poisoned.
Wow.
Ugly and boring.
What a winning combination.
What the fuck has
this got to do with me?
You are an odd specimen.
Not sure what, uh,
phylum you belong in.
Me neither.
That’s something my therapist
and I are really delving in to.
I understand
you are here to kill me.
Something about an accountant?
Your... boyfriend?
We hadn’t put a label on
it, but he was pretty special.
I kill a lot of people,
I suppose some of them
may be accountants. I’m...
I’m sorry I killed yours.
Well, apology not accepted--
You creepy fuck.
Rude...
You are certainly
a... a rare species.
I’m glad I took this
opportunity to get one good,
long, hard look at you.
Okay, but can you do it--
Without,
whacking me on
the head this time.
Fuck.
Balls!
Fuck balls indeed.
I’m getting the feeling
there’s no cookie
and juice after this.
Not for you.
Wait, wait, wait!
Justin...
Did you pull the trigger?
No. I didn’t.
Though I wish I had.
This is going
to take a sec so...
-Sit back, relax.
-Fuck!
-Enjoy the ride.
-What are you doing to me?
Do you know what
exsanguination means?
The drainage of one’s blood.
-
Aah!
I have a few questions.
How do I get to Fizel?
Hey! Where
do you think you’re going?
Get ready to die, you sick fuck!
Justin!
Bravo. Well done!
You know,
I gotta admit Lindy, uh...
Right toward the end there I...
I didn’t think you had it in ya.
So, my apologies.
I decided to take
care of Fizel myself.
What are you covered in?
Is it that time of the month?
But you...
I saw you. How?
The guy in the casket?
No.
Aah, some bum off the street.
Jesus Christ!
Yeah, I just paid
off the coroner, you know?
Why?
I had to
get Fizel out of the way.
But the CIA can’t
operate on US soil.
Even the government,
wouldn’t be dumb
enough to go after him.
Exactly.
Yeah! I needed someone
from the outside, you know?
Someone to draw
the attention away from myself.
Someone who couldn’t
be traced back to me.
So you chose me?
Why?
A glowing
recommendation from Dr. Munchin.
I mean, who do you think funds
his batshit crazy experiments?
But see, I...
I knew you
were something else. Yeah.
My little kamikaze K-9.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Well, in the
Second World War, uh...
they strapped bombs to dogs
and they would train
them to run into enemy tanks.
Right?
The puppies thought they were
just gonna get a treat
or something, but they got
detonated into dog-burger.
Yeah.
So I just had
to figure out what treats
I needed to use
to train you to take out Fizel.
And if you failed or
got killed in the process,
well, you know? Cost me nothing.
That’s why you were perfect.
Where’s my car by the way?
Who the fuck are you?
Who am I?
I’m the only one
keeping this old shitbag
from killing innocent people!
Fizel was an asset
that became a liability.
Everybody wanted him dead,
but nobody can touch him.
And you think this masochistic
piece of shit
was ever gonna stop?
Not so untouchable
anymore, are ya handsome?
Huh?
You lowlife piece of shit.
I’m gonna fucking kill you.
You could try. Or
we just... fuck instead.
What? We had fun, right?
I mean,
you did all this for me?
You must really be into me.
What the fuck?
Was that too strong for ya?
Oh, sorry. I did a bit of
tinkering.
-Ow!
-
You know what though?
It’s gonna turn out to be,
a really beautiful story, Lindy.
-Desperate, little
broken princess
avenges the death
of her lover and then...
takes her own life.
Oops.
You know what’s funny?
I thought you’d be
harder to crack. I really did!
’Cause you seemed
pretty messed up.
You know, in-- in
an interesting way, but...
No, you’re easy.
Well, it turns out all
you needed was to be fucked.
-You know what?
-
It is actually
that time of the month.
Unlucky for you, fuckface.
What the fuck is this?
A parting gift!
Eat shit!
I’m sorry.
-You backstabbing fuck!
-Wait, wait, wait!
I had no idea what
they were going to do with you.
I’m assuming that both
Justin and Fizel are dead?
Uh-huh. Guess who’s next.
No, no, no. Wait,
wait. Remember, we set you free.
Well, yeah I didn’t
think your exposure therapy,
would be quite
so fucking extreme.
Yeah, but look,
it-- it was able to show you
how extraordinary you are.
You served me up
like a lamb to the slaughter.
I had no idea!
But look at you. Lindy.
You’re so special.
I’m a freak. Are
you gonna shoot me?
What?
No, I don’t
think so. I don’t know...
-What have you got that for?
-Sorry.
You’re not
a freak. You’re magnificent.
Now, we can
really start to work.
Now.
Think about the things
that we can do together--
Are you out of
your mind? You betrayed me!
I helped you more than
anybody else in the world.
Fuck you!
-Stop fucking moving.
-Lindy, drop the gun!
-Hold on!
-You’re hurting me!
-Drop the gun! Okay.
-I’m not done!
-Ah, fuck! You shot me!
-Fuck.
Sorry, I thought
you were trying to kill him.
No, you twat! I was
doing your job for you,
-again.
-Don’t call me twat!
Ivan Marcellus Munchin,
you are under arrest
for practicing medicine
without a license.
-Ow!
-All right.
I’m gonna keep pressure on it.
Take your finger
off my leg hole.
Little help?
And the security guards?
Uh, self-defense.
And the incident
with the jumper cables?
Also self-defense.
Self-defense.
And the maternity ward?
Mistaken identity.
What happened
to "living by the rules"?
Some rules are
better than others.
What, does this
mean I’m not going to jail?
You’re going to jail.
You attacked me.
You drove around
the city like a lunatic,
in a car that costs
more than my yearly pay.
You’re going to jail, sweetie.
I see you out front.
-And I’ll see you in court.
-Look forward to it, Detective.
This is every day for me.
They took it off
you in the ambulance.
So, what’s next?
Um, I don’t know,
I start over I guess.
Just... no more blind dates.
Hmm, that’s
probably a good idea.
Lots of creeps out there.
I mean, there are...
some nice guys too.
Yeah.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I’m not gonna find
a bunch of pictures,
of your bumhole on this, am I?
Of my bumhole? No.
What kind of
sleazeball do you think I am?
I mean, the kind
that shoots a woman in the leg.
Yeah.
Well, sorry about that.
Well, you know, I could
always make it up to you.
Dinner sometime?
Um, I’ll--
I’ll think about it.
I’m an excellent cook.
Double down on the halibut.
All right, piss off now.
Spare any change, please?
But...
Do you want that?
Okay.
You’re back.
Can I help you?
I was just
checking it out, you know?
It looks so
beat up from outside.
Who are you?
It’s like
a bomb went off in here.
Yeah, I had a tricky boiler.
But why have you come back?
It’s my apartment.
Well, most people,
when their lives blow up,
would just keep on running.
It is so nice
that you wanted to come home
to try all over again.
Sorry, do I know you?
-Have you been following me?
-Yeah.
What do you actually want?
You are just as
spunky as Munchin described.
You’ve done well under our care.
Okay, I’ve done
enough messing around,
with psychotic therapists
and the fucking CIA,
or whatever you are.
I totally understand.
You’ve spent years being
forced to repress your anger.
I’m sorry about Justin.
What he did was unsanctioned.
But now...
Now Lindy,
you have seen
how powerful you can be
when you embrace your rage.
I’m okay as I am. Thanks.
Really?
Well, how are you?
You’re not normal.
You really think you’d be happy,
living without a purpose?
Through our work, you’ll learn
to harness your rage
and target the right people.
Humans, are the most
powerful, undetectable weapon.
Holy shit!